Benson Vic R. Domingo

Phase 1-B, Brgy. Javalera, Gen. Trias, Cavite +639051577637 | benson.domingo@outlook.com

PROFILE

Licensed Electronics Engineer and Electronics Technician who loves tinkering and has great desire in learning new ideas. Worked as a College Instructor for two and a half years and as a Test Engineer for more than a year, now seeks an opportunity in a company that will help to bring the best out of me by stimulating my passion in electronics and programming through challenges and training.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Bitstop Network Services

Dagupan, Pangasinan

On-the-Job Training

April 8 - May 31, 2013

• Arduino Project: Traffic system with Load Density Sensor

Patria Sable Corpus College

Calao West, Santiago City, Isabela

Instructor - College of Engineering

September 2014 – April 2017

• Taught ECE introductory major courses (Electronic Devices and Circuits, Electronic Circuit Analysis and Design, Electrical Circuits, Logic Circuits)

Maxim Philippines Operating Corp.

Gateway Business Park, Gen. Trias, Cavite

Engineer – Test Systems

July 2017 - Present

- Supported ATE platforms like Flex, MicroFlex, RFx, and ASL3k.
- Solved tester/program related issues up to root cause level.
- Introduced several improvement projects:
 - RFx RF Checker a program developed during the first 6 months of my employment.
 Greatly improved repair time of RFx tester by providing system group a tool for system isolation and troubleshooting.
 - ChatBot A program written in Python Programming Language running on a Raspberry Pi computer which helps support groups in monitoring production tester/set-up. If a set-up encounters a problem, it will immediately notify/chat the group that should respond and fix the problem.

EDUCATION

AMA Computer College

Santiago City, Isabela

Bachelor of Science in Electronics Engineering

2009 - 2014

PRC Licensed Electronics Engineer and Electronics Technician

Sgt. Prospero G. Bello High School

Jones, Isabela

High School Diploma

2004 - 2009

OTHER INFORMATION

Awards

- Best Design Project Proponent GPS Based Motorcycle Tracing and Security System
- Best in PCB Layout Designing

Qualifications

- Programming experience in C/C++ and Python (AVR Microcontroller, Raspberry Pi)
- Basic knowledge in Linux shell and scripting
- Familiar in I2C, SPI, UART communication protocols used in embedded devices
- Experience in using lab equipment (oscilloscope, spectrum analyzer, signal generator)
- Experience in Automated Test Equipment (ATE)
- Fast learner and willing to be trained

Hobbies

- Designing/building homemade electronic projects
- Reading books/online resources, and watching video tutorials

CHARACTER REFERENCE

• Engr. Mark Emerson A. Bernabe

System Planning Engineer

Isabela Electric Cooperative

Contact number: +639351924175

e-mail address: mk iecep@yahoo.com

• Marlyn S. Medted, CPA

Branch Accountant

BDO Unibank, Inc.

Contact number: +639189679599

e-mail address: marlin_smo8@yahoo.com